Profile

As a full-stack engineer with more than six years of experience working on real projects since completing his bachelor's degree in computer science. He specializes in JavaScript or TypeScript with React and Node.js. Have built numerous UIs and highperforming APIs and solved problems according to clients' needs.

Professional Experience

Square, Full-Stack Developer

06/2021 - 03/2023 | San Francisco, United States

- Rebuilt a legacy app and its new features for betting sports games using React Native, Expo, and Firebase, contributing as the main and sometimes unique developer, with each game gaining 1,000 users.
- Built an app where users could select NBA and NFL games, join contests, answer questions, receive notifications, and play against friends.
- Created a dashboard for betting sports games using React and Firebase, allowing admins to sign up for new games and track users and game data.
- Developed cryptocurrency app screens from scratch following a Figma design, using animations and new features from React Native.
- Reviewed pull requests from team members, encouraging them to follow best practices and clean code.

Rogers Communications, Front-End Engineer

08/2020 – 01/2021 | Toronto, on, Canada

- Created dashboard screens for the signup and management of users and building data using React and Redux. Users could request cleaning, internet, or services from the app, and the admin user could manage it from the dashboard.
- Built React Native app screens from scratch for students living in the company buildings.
- Developed a delivery app for a known pharmacy from Brazil, working as the main front-end developer and choosing the front-end project structure.
- Led inexperienced developers to achieve their goals.

Eoin Morgan

Senior Full-Stack Developer

- okaylight0730@gmail.com
- 403-348-3795
- Red Deer, Canada
- C Satosh-J



Education

Bachelor of Computer Science, **Concordia University**

04/2013 - 06/2015 Montreal, Quebec, Canada I 'm highly skilled in designing and implementing database systems, particularly with SQL. I have worked on complex projects where efficient data management was important

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science, University of California,

10/2015 - 04/2017California, United States

"I consider strong communication and teamwork skills to be invaluable assets. During my time at university, I collaborated with multifunctional teams, including designers, project managers, and other developers. I am also adept at effectively communicating technical concepts to non-technical stakeholders to ensure seamless project execution."

Growthsi, Full-Stack Developer

09/2019 - 03/2020 | New York, United States

- Developed a back-end to a system similar to Hotmart, where users could sell online courses and ebooks.
- Worked on the back-end side with Node.js and deployed and tested the Node.js server on AWS.
- Led team members to create alerts and multiple CRUD functions and connect them to multiple foreign APIs.

WildLife Studios(Remote), Software Engineer

02/2016 - 04/2019 | New York, United States

- Created software solutions in partnership with Wildlife Studios.
- Retrieved and manipulated data from games to generate insights, find patterns, and create alerts.
- Developed a platform for marketing and distribution.
- Worked on web development with React, React Native, JavaScript, Node.js, and AWS.



English



Languages: (JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, PHP, HTML5, CSS 3, C#, C++, Java)

FrameWorks & Librares (React & Redux, React Native, Next.JS, Nest.JS, Angular,

Node.JS, Nest.JS, Angular, Node.JS, MobX, Django, Laravel, GoLang, REST APIS)

Other (Programming languages, Agile methodologies, Communication and collaboration, Debugging and troubleshooting, Version control)



Soccer, Travel (I'm a big fan of soccer, not just because it's an exciting and fast-paced sport, but also because it has a rich *history and culture that stretches* back centuries. From the grassroots level to the professional leagues, soccer brings people together from all walks of life, uniting them in their passion for the beautiful game. I love the strategy and teamwork involved in soccer, as well as the individual skill and athleticism that players bring to the field. Whether I'm watching a game on TV or playing in a local league myself, soccer always brings me joy and a sense of connection to the larger global *community of fans and players.")*